(Sheldon:)Now, here's your tartar sauce.
I also brought you salsa.
(Sheldon:)A little unconventional,
but I think you'll like it. It's zingy.
(Sheldon:)And for you, Factory Burrito Grande,
no cheese, no sour cream...
(Sheldon:)...no ugly consequences
from your lactose intolerance.
[SPEAKS IN FRENCH]
(Leonard:)Hang on.
(Leonard:)-Black beans, not pinto beans?
-Yes.
-Guacamole? No cilantro? Lettuce?
-Yep.
-Understand why I'm doing this?
-I do.
(Leonard:)That'll be all.
(Leonard:)That was fun.
[ALL LAUGH]
(Raj:)How long can he keep this up?
(Leonard:)I heard about this professor
who melted down, bought a van...
(Leonard:)...spent the rest of his life
as a dog groomer.
(Raj:)Never went back to the university?
(Leonard:)Only to shampoo
Professor Shamburg's shih tzu.
(Raj:)Sheesh.
You know, I bet if we all chipped in,
we could buy Sheldon a van.
(Raj:)But he's afraid of dogs.
(Leonard:)Yeah. That's the only thing wrong
with that plan.